Zayar Khin

Full-Stack Software Developer Tampa, Florida (813) 360-9266 zkhin@mail.usf.edu

SUMMARY

My passion is to use software and computational approaches to solve industry challenges. I want to help build applications that emphasize great user experiences, and are built with the best practices in software development. My goal is to work with a great team - continuing to learn and contribute to projects that can push the limits of value that software can add to a company.

EXPERIENCE

Moffitt Cancer Center, Tampa FL — Integrated Mathematical Oncology https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Zavar_Khin

May. 2011 - Oct. 2015 Research Associate

- Co-inventor of imaging and computer-assisted biological assay with applications in predicting outcome of chemotherapy - Google Patents
- Managed laboratory operations and developed laboratory workflow and data pipeline for the clinical platform - <u>American Association for Cancer Research</u>
- Predicting drug resistance with >95% accuracy in on-going clinical trials with hundreds of multiple myeloma patients

July 2007 - Mar. 2010 Research Intern/Volunteer

JSURGICAL Inc., Tampa FL — *Laboratory Operations Consultant*

Apr. 2016 - Feb. 2017

- Helped to establish protocols and operations for medical device processing company
- Developed testing and validation procedures for NIST certifications and compliance standards

Visiri — Personal Project

July 2018 - Feb. 2020

- Developed MVP for a deep learning based automated cell counter and management suite for biological research laboratories
- Self-teaching programming and business planning/development
- Familiarized with deep learning libraries and image analysis

PROJECTS

Please see my Portfolio for recent projects.

Portfolio:

https://zkhin.github.io/portfolio/

Github:

https://github.com/zkhin

LinkedIn:

https://linkedin.com/in/zayar-khin

LANGUAGES AND FRAMEWORKS

Main Languages -

JavaScript ES6, Python 3

Web Development -

React, Node.js, Express, JQuery, Django+Flask, SQL/Postgres, Knex, JWT Auth, Cypress/Jest/Enzyme/unit testing

Data Science/Analytics -

NumPy, Pandas, Torch, Matplotlib

SKILLS

Git, Bash, Linux, Windows, Excel, Agile/Scrum workflows, RESTful APIs, Data Structures/Algorithms, AWS, Heroku deployment

EDUCATION

Thinkful — Tampa, FL

Oct. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Engineering Full-Time Immersion Program

- Intensive web development course emphasizing industry best practices including JavaScript, Node.js, React, and algorithms/data structures
- Worked on teams using Agile workflows to complete multiple full-stack web applications under fast deadlines

University of South Florida —

Tampa FL

Aug. 2006 - Oct. 2010

Honors College

Bachelor of Science, Biomedical Sciences

Minor - Psychology

 Undergraduate Scholars Award, University of South Florida - <u>USF</u> News